# **AMBER RENFRO**

4405 Mesa Court, Indianapolis, IN 46241 | (317) 698-3083 | Amber\_Renfro@ymail.com

### **SUMMARY**

Energetic service employee with five years of experience working with the public, looking to elevate the customer service experience at Southwest Airlines. Dedicated to maintaining guest satisfaction as well as contributing to company success by growing customer loyalty. Enjoys working in a fast paced and professional environment.

### **HIGHLIGHTS**

- Five years of experience in customer service.
- Energetic and engaging
- Proven ability to manage multiple projects while meeting deadlines.
- Strong and confident public speaker.
- Hard working, and reliable
- Positive attitude
- Comfortable standing for long periods of time

#### **SKILLS**

- · Communicates well both verbally and in writing
- · Adapts well to changing situations
- · Is cooperative and supportive in a team setting
- · Confident leader
- Strong work ethic
- · Handles conflict well

## **EXPERIENCE**

## April 2013-April 2014

## Assistant Manager, Little Caesars

· I started as a cashier and through dedication and hard work advanced to the position of assistant manager. My responsibilities included daily prep, recording inventory, performing various quality assurance checks, ensuring all products were meeting quality standards, handling money, ensuring all my customers were satisfied with their experience, and leading my crew as the day advanced. I trained new employees as well as coached current employees on ways to improve and better work as a team. I also continued to run a cash register and work in the kitchen alongside my crew.

## April 2014-November 2014

### Delivery Driver, Papa Johns

 Here I worked as a delivery driver. By helping take orders and working in the kitchen with my team I was able to ensure that all orders were delivered complete and on time.

## February 2015 – December 2015

## Delivery Driver/Cook, Pizza Hut

 Here I worked as a delivery driver and a cook. I would work on the line making pizzas, pasta, and wings with my team and also run deliveries. Successful multitasking and teamwork ensured all orders were made and delivered on time.

### January 2016 – Now

Waitress/Hostess/Certified Trainer, Long Horn Steak House

Here I work as a hostess, a waitress, and a certified trainer. As a hostess I greet and seat our guest as well as assist in keeping the facility safe and clean. As a waitress I am responsible for making each of our guest feel welcome in our restaurant. This begins by providing menus and answering any questions our guest may have, as well as making suggestions and upselling products. I'm then responsible for ensuring hot foods are served hot and cold foods are cold, adhering to timing standards for our products and services, and ensuring all guest receive high quality food and beverages. As a certified trainer I am responsible for ensuring all new hires are equipped with the knowledge needed to properly uphold our service standards.

### **EDUCATION**

June 2014 Graduated with Academic Honors from Decatur Central High School

Fall 2014-now degree

Began taking classes part time at both IUPUI and IVY Tech to work towards my engineering